can congress authorize states to enact
regulations or taxes that might
otherwise be unconstitutional
the united states supreme court
considered that question in prudential
insurance company versus benjamin
south carolina taxed foreign insurers
doing business within the state
but it didn't impose the same tax on
in-state insurers
prudential a new jersey insurer selling
insurance in the state
sued south carolina insurance
commissioner george benjamin in an
original proceeding in the south
carolina
supreme court alleging that the tax
unconstitutionally discriminated against
interstate commerce
the state supreme court upheld the tax
and prudential appealed to the united
states supreme court
you